Mystic River Watershed Association Records MS055
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Geographic subject files, 1965 -- 2007; 1970 -- 1985; MS055.002; 21.0 Linear Feet
  - Environmental Notification Form for the Slough Remediation Project, 2005; MS055.002.055.00015 (Box 55)
  - EPA, National Management Measures to Control NonPoint Source Pollution from Urban Areas. 1 of 3 [Binder], 2002; MS055.002.055.00016 (Box 55)
  - EPA, National Management Measures to Control NonPoint Source Pollution from Urban Areas. 2 of 3 [Binder], 2002; MS055.002.055.00017 (Box 55)
  - EPA, National Management Measures to Control NonPoint Source Pollution from Urban Areas. 3 of 3 [Binder], 2002; MS055.002.055.00018 (Box 55)
  - The Establishment and Operation of the Aberjona River Commission [Binder], MS055.002.055.00019 (Box 55)
  - Everett Power Project, Everett, MA. Expanded Environmental Notification Form. 1 of 2, 2006; MS055.002.055.00020 (Box 55)
  - Everett Power Project, Everett, MA. Expanded Environmental Notification Form. 2 of 2, 2006; MS055.002.055.00021 (Box 55)
  - Expanded Environmental Notification Form and Phase One Waiver for Cambridge Discovery Park, 2004; MS055.002.055.00022 (Box 55)
  - Expanded Environmental Notification Form IKEA. 1 of 2 [Binder], 2001; MS055.002.055.00023 (Box 55)
  - Expanded Environmental Notification Form IKEA. 2 of 2 [Binder], 2001; MS055.002.055.00024 (Box 55)
  - Expanded Environmental Notification Form IKEA. 1 of 2 [Binder], 2001; MS055.002.055.00025 (Box 55)
  - Expanded Environmental Notification Form IKEA. 2 of 2 [Binder], 2001; MS055.002.055.00026 (Box 55)
  - Expanded Environmental Notification Form Redstone Shopping Center, Stoneham MA. Volume 1 of 2 [Binder], 2005; MS055.002.056.00001 (Box 56)
  - Expanded Environmental Notification Form, Stoneham Plaza, Volume 2 of 2. Appendix [Binder], 2005; MS055.002.056.00002 (Box 56)
  - The Explorers Guide to the Neponset River Watershed, 1997; MS055.002.056.00003 (Box 56)
  - Extension to Variance for the MRWA CSO Control Plan Lower Charles River Basin Summary Document, 2002; MS055.002.056.00004 (Box 56)
  - Feasibility of Creating a Stormwater Utility, 1999; MS055.002.056.00005 (Box 56)
  - Federal Prgrams Offering Non-Structural Flood Recovery and Flood Plain Mgmt. Alt, 1998; MS055.002.056.00006 (Box 56)
  - Final Environmental Impact Report, Belmont Office/ R&D Building. 1 of 2 [Binder], 2003; MS055.002.056.00007 (Box 56)
  - Final Environmental Impact Report, Belmont Office/ R&D Building. 2 of 2 [Binder], 2003; MS055.002.056.00008 (Box 56)
  - Final Environmental Impact Report, Belmont Office/ R&D Building. [Binder], 2003; MS055.002.056.00009 (Box 56)
  - Final Environmental Impact Report, for Cambridge Discovery Park. 1 of 2 [Binder], 2005; MS055.002.056.00010 (Box 56)
  - Final Environmental Impact Report, for Cambridge Discovery Park. 2 of 2 [Binder], 2005; MS055.002.056.00011 (Box 56)
  - Final Environmental Impact Report,Volume 1, IKEA at Assembly Square, Sommerville MA. 1 of 2 [Binder], 2002; MS055.002.056.00012 (Box 56)
  - Final Environmental Impact Report,Volume 1, IKEA at Assembly Square, Sommerville MA. 2 of 2 [Binder], 2002; MS055.002.056.00013 (Box 56)
  - Final Environmental Impact Report,Volume 2, Appendices, IKEA at Assembly Square, Sommerville MA. [Binder], 2002; MS055.002.056.00014 (Box 56)
  - Final Variance Report for Alewife Brook and the Upper Mystic River. 1 of 2 [Binder], 2003; MS055.002.056.00015 (Box 56)
  - Final Variance Report for Alewife Brook and the Upper Mystic River. 2 of 2 [Binder], 2003; MS055.002.056.00016 (Box 56)
  - Flood Hazard Mitigation Planning: A Community Guide, 1997; MS055.002.056.00017 (Box 56)
  - Fresh Pond Reservation Master Plan Cambridge, MA, 2002; MS055.002.056.00018 (Box 56)
  - Frontage Road Office Center, Environmental Notification Form, 2000; MS055.002.056.00019 (Box 56)
  - Frontage Road Office Center, Environmental Notification Form, 2000; MS055.002.056.00020 (Box 56)
  - Grant and Loan Programs of the MA Executive Office of Environmental Affairs, 2005; MS055.002.056.00021 (Box 56)
  - Guide to Environmental Issues, 1996; MS055.002.056.00022 (Box 56)
  - Handbook for Developing Watershed Plans to Restore and Protect our Waters, Draft. 1 of 2, 2006; MS055.002.056.00023 (Box 56)
  - Handbook for Developing Watershed Plans to Restore and Protect our Waters, Draft. 2 of 2, 2006; MS055.002.056.00024 (Box 56)
  - History of Cooling Water Studies, Mystic Station Units 4-7. 1 of 4 [Binder], 1999; MS055.002.056.00025 (Box 56)
  - History of Cooling Water Studies, Mystic Station Units 4-7. 2 of 4 [Binder], 1999; MS055.002.056.00026 (Box 56)
  - History of Cooling Water Studies, Mystic Station Units 4-7. 3 of 4 [Binder], 1999; MS055.002.056.00027 (Box 56)
  - History of Cooling Water Studies, Mystic Station Units 4-7. 4 of 4 [Binder], 1999; MS055.002.056.00028 (Box 56)
  - The Home Depot Parkway Plaza Shopping Center, Chelsea MA, 2004; MS055.002.057.00001 (Box 57)
  - The Home Depot Parkway Plaza Shopping Center, Locus Map, 2004; MS055.002.057.00002 (Box 57)
  - How You Can Help Your Community to Grow Smart, MS055.002.057.00003 (Box 57)
  - Hydraulic Survey of the Aberjona River and Operation of the Aberjona River Commission, 1973; MS055.002.057.00004 (Box 57)
  - Imprint of the Past: Ecological History of New Bedford Harbor, 2001; MS055.002.057.00005 (Box 57)
  - The Index of Watershed Indicatiors, 1997; MS055.002.057.00006 (Box 57)
  - Leading and Communicating, A Guide for Watershed Partnerships, MS055.002.057.00007 (Box 57)
  - Living Waters Using Benthic Macroinvertebrates and Habitat to Asses Your River's Health, 1997; MS055.002.057.00008 (Box 57)
  - Lower Charles River CSO Variance Response to Public Comments, 2002; MS055.002.057.00009 (Box 57)
  - Macroinvertebrate Data Report for Fall 1997, Spring 1998 and Fall 1998 Samplings [Binder], MS055.002.057.00010 (Box 57)
  - Malden Open space and Receation Plan [Binder], 2001; MS055.002.057.00011 (Box 57)
  - Malden river Ecosystem Restoration Detailed Project Report and Environmental Assessment (Draft) [Binder], 2007; MS055.002.057.00012 (Box 57)
  - The Malden river Ecosystem Restoration Feasibility Study Phase 1, Draft. 1 of 2 [Binder], 2004; MS055.002.057.00013 (Box 57)
  - The Malden river Ecosystem Restoration Feasibility Study Phase 1, Draft. 2 of 2 [Binder], 2004; MS055.002.057.00014 (Box 57)
  - Managing Ecological Risks at EPA: Issues and Recommendations for Progress, 1994; MS055.002.057.00015 (Box 57)
  - Manchester's Environmental Challenge, 2000; MS055.002.057.00016 (Box 57)
  - Massachusetts Environmental Trust 10th Anniversary Report, 1998; MS055.002.057.00017 (Box 57)
  - Massachusetts Office of Coastal Zone Management [Folder], MS055.002.057.00018 (Box 57)
  - Medford Open Space Plan 2000, 2001; MS055.002.057.00019 (Box 57)
  - Medford Phase II Info. [Binder], MS055.002.057.00020 (Box 57)
  - Medford Phase II Info. (Notes and report) [Binder], 2006; MS055.002.057.00021 (Box 57)
  - Merrimack River Initiative Watershed Connections Training Manual for Core VEMN Monitoring Parameters and Methods Final Report [Binder], 1996; MS055.002.057.00022 (Box 57)
  - A Method to Access the Ecological Integrity of Urban Watersheds that Integrates Chemical, Physical and Biological Data [Binder], 1998; MS055.002.057.00023 (Box 57)
  - Methods for Evaluation Wetland Condition #8 Volunteers and Wetland Biomonitoring, 2002; MS055.002.057.00024 (Box 57)
  - Metropolitan District Commission Alewife Reservation and Alewife Brook Master Plan [Binder], 2003; MS055.002.057.00025 (Box 57)
  - Metropolitan District Commission Parkway Restoration: A Master Plan for Segments fo the Alewife Brook and Mystic River Parkways, 1996; MS055.002.057.00026 (Box 57)
  - Mystic/ Alewife Basin Combined Sewer Overflow. 1 of 2 [Binder], 1999; MS055.002.057.00027 (Box 57)
  - Mystic/ Alewife Basin Combined Sewer Overflow. 2 of 2 [Binder], 1999; MS055.002.057.00028 (Box 57)
  - the Mystic River: Inventory, Analysis and Opportunity Draft [Binder], 1997; MS055.002.057.00029 (Box 57)
  - Mystic River Shoreline Management Plan Medford, MA, 1997; MS055.002.057.00030 (Box 57)
  - National List of Plant Species that Occur in Wetlands: Northeast (Region1), 1988; MS055.002.057.00031 (Box 57)
  - National Stormwater Best Managment Practices (BMP) Database: User's Guide, 1999; MS055.002.057.00032 (Box 57)
  - National Resource Inventory and Stewardship Plan of Arlington's Great Meadows in Lexington, MA, 2001; MS055.002.057.00033 (Box 57)
  - Neponset River Estuary Area of Critical Environmental Concern Resource Managment Plan, 1996; MS055.002.057.00034 (Box 57)
  - Neponset River Estuary Area of Critical Environmental Concern Resource Managment Plan, 1996; MS055.002.057.00035 (Box 57)
  - Neponset Watershed Action Plan, 2004; MS055.002.057.00036 (Box 57)
  - New England Environmental Challenges, 2001; MS055.002.057.00037 (Box 57)
  - New England Freshwater Wetlands Invertebrate Biomonitoring Protocol, 1997; MS055.002.057.00038 (Box 57)
  - Notice of Intent Town of Arlington, Arlington High School [Binder], 2004; MS055.002.057.00039 (Box 57)
  - Notice of Noncompliance, NON-NE-00-1002, Investigation Report, Town of Arlington, Department of Public Works, 2000; MS055.002.057.00040 (Box 57)
  - Notice of Project Change for the Long Term CSO Control Plan for Alewife Brook. 1 of 2 [Binder], 2001; MS055.002.058.00001 (Box 58)
  - Notice of Project Change for the Long Term CSO Control Plan for Alewife Brook. 2 of 2 [Binder], 2001; MS055.002.058.00002 (Box 58)
  - Notice of Project Change/ Residences at Acorn Park Belmon/Cambridge, MA. 1 of 3 [Binder], 2007; MS055.002.058.00003 (Box 58)
  - Notice of Project Change/ Residences at Acorn Park Belmon/Cambridge, MA. 2 of 3 [Binder], 2007; MS055.002.058.00004 (Box 58)
  - Notice of Project Change/ Residences at Acorn Park Belmon/Cambridge, MA. 3 of 3 [Binder], 2007; MS055.002.058.00005 (Box 58)
  - Notice of Project Change for Phase One Project for Cambridge Discovery Park, 2005; MS055.002.058.00006 (Box 58)
  - Notice of Project Change, Mystic Center, Medford MA, 2003; MS055.002.058.00007 (Box 58)
  - Notice of Project Change, Residences at Acorn Park, Belmon/Cambridge, MA, 2007; MS055.002.058.00008 (Box 58)
  - Notice of Project Change Tufts University Boathouse at River's Edge, 2004; MS055.002.058.00009 (Box 58)
  - Notice of Project Change Tufts University Boathouse at River's Edge, 2004; MS055.002.058.00010 (Box 58)
  - Notice of Project Change, River's Edge Medford, Everett, and Malden MA, 2005; MS055.002.058.00011 (Box 58)
  - Open Space Assessment and Recommendations for Chelsea and East Boston, 2001; MS055.002.058.00012 (Box 58)
  - Opportunities for Action, 1994; MS055.002.058.00013 (Box 58)
  - Packet Guide to Marine Debris, 2004; MS055.002.058.00014 (Box 58)
  - Paving Our Way to Water Shortages: How Sprawl Aggravates the Effects of Drought, MS055.002.058.00015 (Box 58)
  - Planned Unit Development Assembly Square, Somerville MA, Preliminary Master Plan. 1 of 3 [Binder], 2006; MS055.002.058.00016 (Box 58)
  - Planned Unit Development Assembly Square, Somerville MA, Preliminary Master Plan. 2 of 3 [Binder], 2006; MS055.002.058.00017 (Box 58)
  - Planned Unit Development Assembly Square, Somerville MA, Preliminary Master Plan. 3 of 3 [Binder], 2006; MS055.002.058.00018 (Box 58)
  - Pocket Guide to Marine Debris, 1993; MS055.002.058.00019 (Box 58)
  - Preliminary Data Summary of Urban Storm Water Best Managment Practices, 1999; MS055.002.058.00020 (Box 58)
  - Protecting Water Resources From Hazardous Materials: A Handbook for Local officials, 1987; MS055.002.058.00021 (Box 58)
  - Reading Massachusetts, 2000; MS055.002.058.00022 (Box 58)
  - Ready, Set, Present! a data presentation manual for volunteer water quality monitoring groups [Binder], 1999; MS055.002.058.00023 (Box 58)
  - Release Abatement Measure Status Report 1, Volume 1 of 2. 1 of 2 [Binder], 2005; MS055.002.058.00024 (Box 58)
  - Release Abatement Measure Status Report 1, Volume 1 of 2. 2 of 2 [Binder], 2005; MS055.002.058.00025 (Box 58)
  - A Report Upon the Alewife Fisheries of MA, MS055.002.058.00026 (Box 58)
  - Response to Comments on the Notice of Project Change for the Long Term CSO Control Plan for Alewife Brook. 1 of 3 [Binder], 2003; MS055.002.059.00001 (Box 59)
  - Response to Comments on the Notice of Project Change for the Long Term CSO Control Plan for Alewife Brook. 2 of 3 [Binder], 2003; MS055.002.059.00002 (Box 59)
  - Response to Comments on the Notice of Project Change for the Long Term CSO Control Plan for Alewife Brook. 3 of 3 [Binder], 2003; MS055.002.059.00003 (Box 59)
  - Response to Comments on the Phase 1 Environmental Impact Report and Proposed Section 61 Findings, 2003; MS055.002.059.00004 (Box 59)
  - Response to Comments on the Phase 1 Environmental Impact Report and Proposed Section 61 Findings, 2003; MS055.002.059.00005 (Box 59)
  - Response to Comments on the Phase 1 Environmental Impact Report and Proposed Section 61 Findings, 2003; MS055.002.059.00006 (Box 59)
  - Request for Amendment to Amended Order of Conditions, Tufts University Boathouse, 2005; MS055.002.059.00007 (Box 59)
  - The Ripple Effect: How to make Waves in the turbulent world of watershed cleanup plans, 2001; MS055.002.059.00008 (Box 59)
  - River Monitoring Study Design Workbook, MS055.002.059.00009 (Box 59)
  - Sediment Quality of Lakes, Rivers, and Estuaries in the Mystic River Basin, Eastern MA, 2001-2003, MS055.002.059.00010 (Box 59)
  - Sediment Quality of Lakes, Rivers, and Estuaries in the Mystic River Basin, Eastern MA, 2001-2003, MS055.002.059.00011 (Box 59)
  - Sediment Quality of Lakes, Rivers, and Estuaries in the Mystic River Basin, Eastern MA, 2001-2003, MS055.002.059.00012 (Box 59)
  - Selected Articles in Grassroots Fundraising, 1999; MS055.002.059.00013 (Box 59)
  - Smart Growth for clean Water: Helping Communities Address the Water Quality Impacts of Sprawl, 2003; MS055.002.059.00014 (Box 59)
  - State of the Environment 2006, Environmental League of MA, MS055.002.059.00015 (Box 59)
  - Stoneham Executive Center, 2002; MS055.002.059.00016 (Box 59)
  - Stormwater Management in Somerville, MA: A Cost-Benefit Approach, 2004; MS055.002.059.00017 (Box 59)
  - Stormwater Monitoring Work Plan for the Upper Mystic River Draft, 1999; MS055.002.059.00018 (Box 59)
  - Stormwater Strategies, 1999; MS055.002.059.00019 (Box 59)
  - Strategic Planning Course No. OMS 509 Antioch New England Graduate School, 1996; MS055.002.059.00020 (Box 59)
  - Summary of the August 14-15 2002, Experts Workshop on Public Health Impacts of Sewer Overflows, MS055.002.059.00021 (Box 59)
  - Supplemental Draft Environmental Impact Report Stoneham Executive Center (Vol. 1 of 2), 2002; MS055.002.059.00022 (Box 59)
  - Supplemental Draft Environmental Impact Report Stoneham Executive Center, 2002; MS055.002.059.00023 (Box 59)
  - Supplemental Draft Environmental Impact Report, Technical Appendices (Vol. 2 of 2) Stoneham Executive Center. 1 of 3, 2002; MS055.002.059.00024 (Box 59)
  - Supplemental Draft Environmental Impact Report, Technical Appendices (Vol. 2 of 2) Stoneham Executive Center. 2 of 3, 2002; MS055.002.059.00025 (Box 59)
  - Supplemental Draft Environmental Impact Report, Technical Appendices (Vol. 2 of 2) Stoneham Executive Center. 3 of 3, 2002; MS055.002.059.00026 (Box 59)
  - Supplemental Draft Environmental Impact Report, Responses to Comments on the DIER, Stoneham Executive Center. 1 of 3, 2002; MS055.002.059.00027 (Box 59)
  - Supplemental Draft Environmental Impact Report, Responses to Comments on the DIER, Stoneham Executive Center. 2 of 3, 2002; MS055.002.059.00028 (Box 59)
  - Supplemental Draft Environmental Impact Report, Responses to Comments on the DIER, Stoneham Executive Center. 3 of 3, 2002; MS055.002.059.00029 (Box 59)
  - Survey of Reports and Data on Rainfall and Flooding for the Alewife Brook Area of Arlington, Belmont, and Cambridge, 2002; MS055.002.060.00001 (Box 60)
  - Survey of Reports and Data on Rainfall and Flooding for the Alewife Brook Area, CD. 1 of 3 [Binder], 2003; MS055.002.060.00002 (Box 60)
  - Survey of Reports and Data on Rainfall and Flooding for the Alewife Brook Area. 2 of 3 [Binder], 2003; MS055.002.060.00003 (Box 60)
  - Survey of Reports and Data on Rainfall and Flooding for the Alewife Brook Area. 3 of 3 [Binder], 2003; MS055.002.060.00004 (Box 60)
  - Town of Arlington Open Space and Recreation Plan [Binder], 1996 -- 2001; MS055.002.060.00005 (Box 60)
  - Town of Belmont Open Space and Recreation Plan [Binder], 2001; MS055.002.060.00006 (Box 60)
  - Town of Burlington Open Space and Recreation Plan [Binder], 1996; MS055.002.060.00007 (Box 60)
  - Town of Reading Admission to the MA Water Resources Authority, Waterworks System, Envrionmental Impact Report[Binder], 2002; MS055.002.060.00008 (Box 60)
  - Town of Stoneham MA, Open Space and Recreation Plan Uptdate, 1997; MS055.002.060.00009 (Box 60)
  - Town of Wakefield Open Space and Recreation Plan [Binder], 2000; MS055.002.060.00010 (Box 60)
  - Town of Winchester Aberjona River Flood Improvement: Corss Street Culvert Notice of Project Change [Binder], 2003; MS055.002.060.00011 (Box 60)
  - Town of Winchester Aberjona River Flood Improvement, Expanded Environmental Notification (Copy 1) [Binder], 2003; MS055.002.060.00012 (Box 60)
  - Town of Winchester Aberjona River Flood Improvement, Expanded Environmental Notification (Copy 2) [Binder], 2003; MS055.002.060.00013 (Box 60)
  - Tufts University Boathouse, 2005; MS055.002.060.00014 (Box 60)
  - Tufts University Boathouse, Request for Amended Order of Conditions, 2005; MS055.002.060.00015 (Box 60)
  - Turning the Tide on Trash: A learning Guide on Marine Debris, 1992; MS055.002.060.00016 (Box 60)
  - University of Massachusetts Annual Conference Watershed Conservation, 2002; MS055.002.060.00017 (Box 60)
  - Upper Mystic Lake Dam, Draft Conceptual Design Submittal, 2004; MS055.002.060.00018 (Box 60)
  - USGS-DEP-DEM Cooperative Program, 2000; MS055.002.060.00019 (Box 60)
  - Volunteer Stream Monitoring: A Methods Manual, 1997; MS055.002.060.00020 (Box 60)
  - Water from Source to Sea Newsletter, 2006; MS055.002.060.00021 (Box 60)
  - Water Quality Report 1961, Mystic River Watershed. 1 of 2 [Binder], 1965; MS055.002.060.00022 (Box 60)
  - Water Quality Report 1961, Mystic River Watershed. 2 of 2 [Binder], 1965; MS055.002.060.00023 (Box 60)
  - Water Resources Development, 1991; MS055.002.060.00024 (Box 60)
  - Water Wisdom 2nd Edition, MS055.002.060.00025 (Box 60)
  - Watershed Resource Guide: Tools for Protecting New England Watersheds, 1999; MS055.002.060.00026 (Box 60)
  - Wetland Bioassessment Fact Sheets, 1998; MS055.002.060.00027 (Box 60)
  - Wildlife Invetory: Alewife Reservation, Eastern End Cambridge, MA, 1997; MS055.002.060.00028 (Box 60)
  - the Woonasquatucket River Watershed, MS055.002.060.00029 (Box 60)
  - Yacht Clubs' Private uses of Publicly-Owned Land Along the Mystic River. 1 of 2, 2003; MS055.002.060.00030 (Box 60)
  - Yacht Clubs' Private uses of Publicly-Owned Land Along the Mystic River. 2 of 2, 2003; MS055.002.060.00031 (Box 60)
- General subject files, 1924 -- 1993; 1967 -- 1990; MS055.003; 23.65 Linear Feet
  This series contains correspondence, reports, legal documents, brochures, newsclippings, and similar documents concerning a multitude of geographical entities and scientific topics.
  This series is arranged by subject.
  - Notes relative to industri-plex 128, Commerce Way, Woburn, 1981; MS055.003.008.00001 (Box 8)
  - Briefing package to Little Pond Committee, 1985; MS055.003.008.00002 (Box 8)
  - Wetland Number 9, 1979; MS055.003.008.00003 (Box 8)
  - Response to comments, MS055.003.008.00004 (Box 8)
    No Date available
  - Is the flooding of Alewife Brook a mere local phenomenon?, 1976; MS055.003.008.00005 (Box 8)
  - Alewife open space plan, 1984 -- 1985; MS055.003.008.00006 (Box 8)
  - Alewife, 1979 -- 1986; MS055.003.008.00007 (Box 8)
  - Alewife history, 1982; MS055.003.008.00008 (Box 8)
  - MRWA comments on draft E.I.S., Red Line extension, Harvard Square to Arlington Heights, 1977; MS055.003.008.00009 (Box 8)
  - An access oriented parking strategy for the Boston Metropolitan Area: appendices, 1974; MS055.003.008.00010 (Box 8)
  - An access oriented parking strategy for the Boston Metropolitan Area: summary report, 1974; MS055.003.008.00011 (Box 8)
  - Massachusetts water quality standards: implementation policy for the abatement of pollution from CSOs, 1990; MS055.003.008.00012 (Box 8)
  - Massachusetts G.L.C. 131s40: notice of intent, 1979; MS055.003.008.00013 (Box 8)
  - Report of the Transportation Studies Sub-committee of the Joint Regional Transportation Subcommittee on the Public Participation Process of the Alewife Station area, 1981; MS055.003.008.00014 (Box 8)
  - Public hearing on the draft environmental impact statement/report for the Rt. 2-Alewife Brook Parkway project, 1987; MS055.003.008.00015 (Box 8)
  - Draft environmental overview summary for transportation improvements in the Alewife corridor of Cambridge, Arlington, and Belmont, 1975; MS055.003.008.00016 (Box 8)
  - Traffic impact analysis, Alewife MBTA Station location alternatives, 1980; MS055.003.008.00017 (Box 8)
  - Alewife: Red Line extension project, 1977; MS055.003.008.00018 (Box 8)
  - Alewife area subsurface study, summary report, 1978; MS055.003.008.00019 (Box 8)
  - Alewife open space technical memoranda, MS055.003.008.00020 (Box 8)
    No Date Available
  - Natural flood storage in the Little River/Alewife Brook watershed, 1985; MS055.003.008.00021 (Box 8)
  - Alewife court case, 1986 -- 1987; MS055.003.008.00022 (Box 8)
  - Alternatives for Alewife open space, 1977; MS055.003.008.00023 (Box 8)
  - Traffic counts, Alewife Station vicinity, 1987; MS055.003.008.00024 (Box 8)
  - Rt. 2/Alewife Brook Parkway project, draft E.I.R., 1987; MS055.003.008.00025 (Box 8)
    First of two parts.
  - Rt. 2/Alewife Brook Parkway project, draft E.I.R., 1987; MS055.003.008.00026 (Box 8)
    Second of two parts.
  - Harvard Square Red Line extension informational brochure, 1975; MS055.003.008.00027 (Box 8)
  - Alewife, 1984 -- 1989; MS055.003.008.00028 (Box 8)
  - Alewife, 1982 -- 1985; MS055.003.008.00029 (Box 8)
  - Alewife, 1981 -- 1983; MS055.003.008.00030 (Box 8)
  - Alewife, 1974 -- 1978; MS055.003.008.00031 (Box 8)
  - The Alewife study, 1974; MS055.003.008.00032 (Box 8)
  - Alewife urban design: alternatives report, 1977; MS055.003.008.00033 (Box 8)
  - Open space, human use environmental concerns: northwest, 1972; MS055.003.008.00034 (Box 8)
  - Inwood Office Park, Woburn: final E.I.R., 1988; MS055.003.008.00035 (Box 8)
  - Spy Pond Phase II restoration: environmenal notification form, 1987; MS055.003.008.00036 (Box 8)
  - Wetlands: Arlington and Cambridge, 1985; MS055.003.008.00037 (Box 8)
  - Combined sewer overflow, 1979; MS055.003.009.00001 (Box 9)
  - Combined sewer overflow program: Inner Harbor facilities plan (draft-update) figures, 1979; MS055.003.009.00002 (Box 9)
  - Combined sewer overflow program: Inner Harbor facilities plan (draft-update) tables, 1979; MS055.003.009.00003 (Box 9)
  - Combined sewer overflow program: Inner Harbor facilities plan (draft-update) chapters III-IX, 1979; MS055.003.009.00004 (Box 9)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan: "technical memorandum 2-3: planning area water uses and water quality standards", 1988; MS055.003.009.00005 (Box 9)
  - Certificate of the Secretary of Environmental Affairs on the environmental notification form, 1988; MS055.003.009.00006 (Box 9)
  - Combined Sewer Overflow Subcommittee of Facilties Planning Citizens Advisory Committee [FPCAC], 1988; MS055.003.009.00007 (Box 9)
  - Combined sewer overflow abatement in the Charles River Basin study area: public hearing, 1980; MS055.003.009.00008 (Box 9)